Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 58
  - Strughold: "Effects of high altitude after interruption,", 11 April 1940 (Box-folder 58: 9)
  - Heintzelmann: "Wing spar flange of the Fw 300A with 1620 steel treated to 120kg/mm,", 27 November 1943 (Box-folder 58: 10)
  - Kussner: "Contributions to the Instationary airfoil theory German microfilm 119,", 25 January 1940 (Box-folder 58: 11)
  - Heise: "Testing of a new roller slat-drive,", undated (Box-folder 58: 12)
  - Heinkel: "Contruction directives for riveting(general),", undated (Box-folder 58: 13)
  - Kussner: "Contributions to the instationary airfoil VI on the effect of shock-waves on airfoils,", August 1937 (Box-folder 58: 14)
  - Hoerner: "Influence of compressibility on drag,", January 1944 (Box-folder 58: 15)
  - Wagger: "Development of jet-pumps,", undated (Box-folder 58: 16)
  - Wehrse: "Temporary work unstruction for the contruction of airtight cabins of TA 152H,", undated (Box-folder 58: 17)
  - Weber: "Plastics for the construction of aircraft parts,", January 1945 (Box-folder 58: 18)
  - Zimmermann: "Theoretical treatment of the (control surface) overhauling balance,", 21 May 1940 (Box-folder 58: 19)
  - Weyde: "Projected turbojet fighter with two HeS011 engines,", November 1944 (Box-folder 58: 20)
  - Goettingen: "Wind tunnel tests on various wing profiles,", 28 June 1941 (Box-folder 58: 21)
  - Messerschmidt: "Bibliography on spin,", undated (Box-folder 58: 22)
  - DVL: "High speed wind tunnel tests on the He 177 bomber,", undated (Box-folder 58: 23)
  - Wysock: "3-component tests on aircraft snow-runners,", 15 March 1941 (Box-folder 58: 24)
  - Ruden: "Wind tunnel tests on a rotation dimensional collector-diffusor,", undated (Box-folder 58: 25)
- Box 59
  - "Ermittlung des profilwiderstandes aus dem impulsverlust,", undated (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Kinder: "A simple instrument using decimeter waves to palce mving objects capable of reflecting these waves,", October 1944 (Box-folder 59: 2)
  - "Tests with a "running-in" fluid for new brake linings,", February 1942 (Box-folder 59: 3)
  - Heckmann: "Dielectrics-type antenna,", November 1938 (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - "Proposal for the direct jamming of ground observation devices by means of pulse transmitters,", December 1944 (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - H. Lindemann: "High speed measuremnets on a Me 163B tailless airplanes model with non-twisted wing,", October 1944 (Box-folder 59: 6)
  - H. Schlichting: "The aerodynamic forces due to the mutual interferences between the several parts of an airplane,", June 1946 (Box-folder 59: 7)
  - O. Stokes: "Kapitel VII Sehr langsame bewegung,", undated (Box-folder 59: 8)
- Box 60
  - G. V. Trentini: "Antennas for ultrahigh-frequency warning devices,", September 1944 (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - W. Linke: "Comparison of diverse cooling systems,", 1940 (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - V. Wersin: "Combination cockpit-heater and window defrosting system for FW 200 transport,", October 1942 (Box-folder 60: 3)
  - W. Kerris: "Electrotechnical requirements for the construction of inductive transmitters insensitive to interferences, A contribution to the theory of the bridge of the force measuring unit,", undated (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - M. Hansen: "Three component measurements on sweptback wings with split flaps,", June 1946 (Box-folder 60: 5)
  - K. Voels: Measurements on two laminar profiles at high Reynolds numbers,", May 1946 (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - F. Kai and W. Tollmien: "Application of the mathematical treatment of shock fronts and vortex flow to a body consisting of a cone and cylinder,", September 1944 (Box-folder 60: 7)
  - "Laminar boundary layer with suction and air discharge,", 15 April 1944 (Box-folder 60: 8)
  - Schmidt: "Electrum tube with low noise level,", November 1942 (Box-folder 60: 9)
  - K. Loeffler: "Tests of "Luvitherm" insulating materials,", May 1941 (Box-folder 60: 10)
  - "The automatic DF set E 351 D WN,", January 1945 (Box-folder 60: 11)
  - M. Stockel: "Instruction manual on electron, a magnesium alloy,", undated (Box-folder 60: 12)
  - F. Wilkens: "Tests of L5 elektron alloy for aircraft construction,", Febuary 1945 (Box-folder 60: 13)
- Box 61
  - Schwarz: "Contributions to the instationary airfoil theory IV,", undated (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Schiller: "Generalization of the similarity laws of (252) 2nd report,", undated (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - S. Sokoloff: "Influences of ultra-sonic waves on the solidification process of cast metals,", 11 August 1935 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Schwarz: "Contributions to the in-stationary airfoil theory,", circa 1939 (Box-folder 61: 4)
  - G. Plato: "On stability conditions in curve flight,", circa 1941 (Box-folder 61: 5)
  - Ruppelt: "Investigation of spotwelding of alloyed heat treatable steels,", September 1943 (Box-folder 61: 6)
  - Ruff: "Attempts at rescue from high altitudes,", 1992-1943 (Box-folder 61: 7)
  - W. Pfenninger: "Investigations on friction decrease of airfoils, especially by means of boundary layer bleeding by suctions,", undated (Box-folder 61: 8)
  - H. Schrode: "Stiffnesses of various tires,", 16 October 1941 (Box-folder 61: 9)
  - Schroedter: "Tables for determination of the critical mach number,", undated (Box-folder 61: 10)
  - Schwarz: "Contributions to the Instationary airfoil theory VII,", undated (Box-folder 61: 11)
  - Wehrse: "Characteristics of Plexiglass,", 11 September 1940 (Box-folder 61: 12)
  - Wehrse: "Discussion on sealing problems,", 28 March 1944 (Box-folder 61: 13)
  - Wendland: "Heating and ventilation of airplanes,", undated (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - Schiller: "Oscillations of flat rectangular plates in subsonic flow,", undated (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - Schiller: "Influence of flat tail fins in the front of the plate subject to airflow on its oscillation behavior,", undated (Box-folder 61: 16)
  - Brennecke and Keydell: "Tests on a roll-angle stabile flight body,", undated (Box-folder 61: 17)
  - V. Bordely: "The air forces on a harmonically oscillating two-dimensional wing at supersonic speeds,", 6 November 1939 (Box-folder 61: 18)
  - Bauer: "Investigation of the applicability of a receiver equipped with lead sulfide cells for navigation in fog,", undated (Box-folder 61: 19)
- Box 62
  - Goettingen: "wind tunnel tests on various wing profiles,", circa 1941 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Schwier: "Tests on drag changes of an airfoil in blowing out heated air,", undated (Box-folder 62: 2)
  - W. Schwier: "Blow-out tests for lift increase on a wing of 9% thickness with slat and flap,", undated (Box-folder 62: 3)
  - T. Schwenk: "Tests on a trapeze swept-wing,", 31 March 1943 (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Tollmien and Schafer: "Rotational symmtric supersonic flows,", January 1947 (Box-folder 62: 5)
  - Betrifft: "Widerstand von Auβenbehaltern,", 9 Febuary 1945 (Box-folder 62: 6)
  - Grebe: "Profile drag tests for painted wings,", November 1944 (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Eisenmann: "Investigation of an automatic dive pull-out for the Me 210 part II,", 19 July 1941 (Box-folder 62: 8)